<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Big Tech on Notes</title>
    <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/big-tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Big Tech on Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/big-tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Is the protection of privacy worthwhile</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/big-tech/is-the-protection-of-privacy-worthwhile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/big-tech/is-the-protection-of-privacy-worthwhile/</guid>
      <description>Is the protection of privacy worthwhile? Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/is-the-protection-of-privacy-worthwhilegp-essay-5/
Individual privacy has been at the forefront of debates for years with many across the globe constantly weighing the need for privacy against the need for governments to monitor what people are doing in order to prevent events of mass terror. With the rise in terror attacks in the past five years in particular, this discussion has become more critical than ever. The question that needs to be addressed is whether the protection of privacy and thus people’s rights to not have their lives monitored is worth the risks of allowing terrorism, violence and crime to continue to grow, and my view is that the protection of privacy is worthwhile to the extent that it does not impinge on the need for governments to protect the safety and welfare of their people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is there still privacy in today&#39;s world especially given the need for national security</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/big-tech/is-there-still-privacy-in-todays-world-especially-given-the-need-for-national-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/big-tech/is-there-still-privacy-in-todays-world-especially-given-the-need-for-national-security/</guid>
      <description>Is there still privacy in today&amp;rsquo;s world especially given the need for national security? Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/gp-essay-45-is-there-still-privacy-in-todays-world-especially-given-the-need-for-national-security/
“To be left alone is the most precious thing one can ask of the modern world,” quipped English writer Anthony Burgess. While alluding to solitude and being alone, this quote has seen greater relevance in modern times with respect to one’s privacy. Privacy – the ability of an individual to keep information regarding him away from the knowledge of others – is becoming an increasingly debatable issue.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
