<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home title on Notes</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home title on Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello world!</title>
      <link>/hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 14:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hello_world/</guid>
      <description>Hello world!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Hugo</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a static site engine written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 Cobra Viper J Walter Weatherman Cast  Learn more and contribute on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/gender/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/gender/readme/</guid>
      <description>Gender Discrimination Sexism in Tech The Elizabeth Holmes Trial Is a Wake-Up Call for Sexism in Tech - Ellen Pao (15/09/2021)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/readme/</guid>
      <description>Prejudice and Discrimination According to a 2021 Study by the New York University, the more an academic discipline is perceived to require raw talent or &amp;ldquo;brilliance&amp;rdquo; for success, the more both women and early-career academics feel professionally inadequate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/el-notes/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/readme/</guid>
      <description>EL Notes If you want, please compile all statistics and data you find in this repository. For EL4131. Additional articles are also appreciated.
Directory Structure ├── Science and Technology │ ├── _index.m │ ├── Tech │ │ ├── Tech Talent Crunch │ │ │ ├── NTU traffic prediction technology bags prizes at Waymo autonomous driving competition - The Straits Times │ │ │ ├── 6,500 new financial sector jobs in 2021 amid shortage of S&#39;poreans to fill rising number of tech roles - TODAY │ │ │ ├── _index.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/science/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/science/readme/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The danger of modern science is that instead of teaching mankind humility, it has made us supremely arrogant.&amp;rdquo; Comment. In his bestselling book ‘Homo Deus: A Brief History of Tomorrow’, Professor Yuval Noah Harari commented that “during the Agricultural Revolution, humankind silenced animals and plants, and turned the animist grand opera into a dialogue between man and gods. During the Scientific Revolution, humankind silenced the gods too.” In fact, the very premise of Harari’s seemingly outlandish claims is that modern science has made men gods; although the best and the brightest understand that scientific research simply reflects the inadequacy of human knowledge, the accessibility and transformative power of modern science has granted us an immeasurable amount of power which we are wont to abuse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/theranos/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/theranos/readme/</guid>
      <description>Theranos Theranos has been a very clear indicator of how much trust we have in technology today. The scandal was one of the many such cases involving market fraud and the misleading of shareholders over the past few years and has been helmed as Silicon Valley’s Greatest Disaster. With an idea as incredible as was the founder’s, Elizabeth Holmes, who possessed a very limited amount of knowledge regarding medical trials and entrepreneurial methods and a small patent developed within a few five days, Theranos seemed doomed from the start, yet it grew from a simple start-up in 2003 to a highly valued company with a valuation of about 9 billion dollars in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>As science advances, the human race regresses. Is this a fair comment</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/science/as-science-advances-the-human-race-regresses.-is-this-a-fair-comment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/science/as-science-advances-the-human-race-regresses.-is-this-a-fair-comment/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;As science advances, the human race regresses.&amp;rdquo; Is this a fair comment? Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/gp-essay-24-as-science-advances-the-human-race-regresses-is-this-a-fair-comment/
“All of the biggest technological inventions created by man say little about his intelligence, but speak volumes about his laziness.” This quote, widely attributed to Mark Kennedy, does indeed speak volumes about the questions which we are confronted with today: has scientific discovery advanced, while the human race languishes, and even regresses? With increasingly brave forays into the fields of artificial intelligence, neuroscience, genetic engineering, as well as broader and long-ranging explorations of the universe, we are breaking frontiers barely dreamt about just a generation ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Courts and Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/ai/courts-and-artifical-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/ai/courts-and-artifical-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>Source: https://www.iacajournal.org/articles/10.36745/ijca.343/ Outline: https://outline.com/xPzKEw
International Journal for Court Administration 1. Introduction Machines are taking over the work of people everywhere. In the not too distant past, spell-checking and search engines were regarded by many as ‘intelligent’ information technology. Today, facial recognition routinely checks travelers at our airports. Google Maps gives me unsolicited advice about my destination: “the restaurant may be closed”. My tablet and my mobile phone answer my spoken questions with friendly spoken replies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diversity brought about by globalization should be celebrated, not feared. Discuss</title>
      <link>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/diversity-brought-about-by-globalization-should-be-celebrated-not-feared.-discuss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/diversity-brought-about-by-globalization-should-be-celebrated-not-feared.-discuss/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Diversity brought about by globalization should be celebrated, not feared.&amp;rdquo; Discuss. Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/diversity-brought-about-by-globalization-should-be-celebrated-not-feared-discuss-gp-essay-4/
The world today is more diverse than it has ever been. The advent of globalisation, increasing ease of communication and movement has allowed many different cultures, languages, traditions and beliefs to permeate the world, no longer completely separated by geographical boundaries. This increased diversity has led to many positive effects on the world at large such as greater international cooperation, greater economic growth and improvements to the overall standards of healthcare as the exchange of information becomes more fluid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment, not truth, is the priority of the media today, Comment</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/cancel-culture/entertainment-not-truth-is-the-priority-of-the-media-today-comment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/cancel-culture/entertainment-not-truth-is-the-priority-of-the-media-today-comment/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Entertainment, not truth, is the priority of the media today,&amp;rdquo; Comment. Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/gp-essay-11-entertainment-not-truth-is-the-priority-of-the-media-today-comment/
Will Rogers once said, “All I know is just what I read in the papers, and that’s an alibi for my ignorance.” It is now fashionable to degrade the media for obscuring verifiable facts that is in the public interest to be made aware in favour of providing amusement and enjoyment to its audience. However, it is important to recognise that media is not a homogenous collective and the priorities of the media cannot be reduced to a simple dichotomy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethics in Science is more beneficial that the Science itself. Do you agree</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/science/ethics/ethics-in-science-is-more-beneficial-that-the-science-itself.-do-you-agree/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/science/ethics/ethics-in-science-is-more-beneficial-that-the-science-itself.-do-you-agree/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Ethics in Science is more beneficial that the Science itself.&amp;rdquo; Do you agree? Question Analysis:
 &amp;ldquo;beneficial&amp;rdquo;:  Benefitted whom?: Humans.    &amp;ldquo;Ethics in Science&amp;rdquo;:  Points Against    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How big tech manipulates academia to avoid regulation</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/ai/how-big-tech-manipulates-academia-to-avoid-regulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/ai/how-big-tech-manipulates-academia-to-avoid-regulation/</guid>
      <description>How big tech manipulates academia to avoid regulation Source: https://theintercept.com/2019/12/20/mit-ethical-ai-artificial-intelligence/
The irony of the ethical scandal enveloping Joichi Ito, the former director of the MIT Media Lab, is that he used to lead academic initiatives on ethics. After the revelation of his financial ties to Jeffrey Epstein, the financier charged with sex trafficking underage girls as young as 14, Ito resigned from multiple roles at MIT, a visiting professorship at Harvard Law School, and the boards of the John D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How effective are prisons in addressing the problem of crime</title>
      <link>/el-notes/crime-and-punishment/how-effective-are-prisons-in-addressing-the-problem-of-crime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/crime-and-punishment/how-effective-are-prisons-in-addressing-the-problem-of-crime/</guid>
      <description>How effective are prisons in addressing the problem of crime? Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/gp-essay-35-how-effective-are-prisons-in-addressing-the-problem-of-crime/
In the words of Michel Foucault, a French intellectual, prison is “but a recruitment center for the army of crime.” In a time when citizens are increasingly questioning the effectiveness of the criminal justice system and recidivism rates are on the rise, it is necessary to question the effectiveness of imprisonment in mitigating crime. Whether incarceration is successful in eradicating crime thus rests on whether it successfully reforms criminals and whether the act of imprisonment promotes crime in communities in the long term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How far is it possible to have a fair and inclusive society in your country</title>
      <link>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/how-far-is-it-possible-to-have-a-fair-and-inclusive-society-in-your-country/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/how-far-is-it-possible-to-have-a-fair-and-inclusive-society-in-your-country/</guid>
      <description>How far is it possible to have a fair and inclusive society in your country? Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/gp-essay-22-how-far-is-it-possible-to-have-a-fair-and-inclusive-society-in-your-country/
In a meritocratic, pluralistic nation such as Singapore, what does it mean for a society to be ‘fair’ and ‘inclusive’? When there is fairness, the treatment of all individuals is not predicated on indicators which are out of his control, such as race or religion. When a society is inclusive, all members benefit from progress and equality of opportunity, diversity is celebrated instead of shunned, and all individuals are allowed to participate in deciding the creation and direction of social institutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How far is the trend towards diversity a positive development</title>
      <link>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/how-far-is-the-trend-towards-diversity-a-positive-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/how-far-is-the-trend-towards-diversity-a-positive-development/</guid>
      <description>How far is the trend towards diversity a positive development? Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/gp-essay-13-how-far-is-the-trend-towards-diversity-a-positive-development/
Many renowned universities such as Harvard are known for admitting students who come from different countries and from different walks of life. The rationale behind this is that their students need to learn how to interact with people with a variety of backgrounds in order to become effective global citizens. Indeed, globalization has made societies today much more diverse since one end of the world is just a plane ride away from the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In an age of rapid technological advancement, is a single career for life realistic</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/in-an-age-of-rapid-technological-advancement-is-a-single-career-for-life-realistic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/in-an-age-of-rapid-technological-advancement-is-a-single-career-for-life-realistic/</guid>
      <description>In an age of rapid technological advancement, is a single career for life realistic? Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/gp-essay-38-in-an-age-of-rapid-technological-advancement-is-a-single-career-for-life-realistic/
A recent LinkedIn survey found that if you are less than 32 years old, you are likely to change jobs at least four times before you reach that age. By 2001, only half of the workforce in the United Kingdom had been in continuous employment for a period longer than four years. Yet another survey by staffing firm Robert Half found that 64% of workers favour what is known as ‘job-hopping’, particularly the younger generation, with 75% of employees under 34 believing in the benefits of job-hopping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the protection of privacy worthwhile</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/big-tech/is-the-protection-of-privacy-worthwhile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/big-tech/is-the-protection-of-privacy-worthwhile/</guid>
      <description>Is the protection of privacy worthwhile? Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/is-the-protection-of-privacy-worthwhilegp-essay-5/
Individual privacy has been at the forefront of debates for years with many across the globe constantly weighing the need for privacy against the need for governments to monitor what people are doing in order to prevent events of mass terror. With the rise in terror attacks in the past five years in particular, this discussion has become more critical than ever. The question that needs to be addressed is whether the protection of privacy and thus people’s rights to not have their lives monitored is worth the risks of allowing terrorism, violence and crime to continue to grow, and my view is that the protection of privacy is worthwhile to the extent that it does not impinge on the need for governments to protect the safety and welfare of their people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is there still privacy in today&#39;s world especially given the need for national security</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/big-tech/is-there-still-privacy-in-todays-world-especially-given-the-need-for-national-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/big-tech/is-there-still-privacy-in-todays-world-especially-given-the-need-for-national-security/</guid>
      <description>Is there still privacy in today&amp;rsquo;s world especially given the need for national security? Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/gp-essay-45-is-there-still-privacy-in-todays-world-especially-given-the-need-for-national-security/
“To be left alone is the most precious thing one can ask of the modern world,” quipped English writer Anthony Burgess. While alluding to solitude and being alone, this quote has seen greater relevance in modern times with respect to one’s privacy. Privacy – the ability of an individual to keep information regarding him away from the knowledge of others – is becoming an increasingly debatable issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People are placing too much faith in medical science. Do you agree</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/science/people-are-placing-too-much-faith-in-medical-science.-do-you-agree/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/science/people-are-placing-too-much-faith-in-medical-science.-do-you-agree/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;People are placing too much faith in medical science.&amp;rdquo; Do you agree? Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/gp-essay-18-people-are-placing-too-much-faith-in-medical-science-do-you-agree/
“A gramme is better than a damn.” The subtle yet incredibly potent phrase is continuously remembered by the members of a seemingly utopian society in Aldous Huxley’s novel ‘Brave New World’ whenever they feel unhappy. They spontaneously turn to a gramme of soma, a narcotic touted to be a medical marvel that subdues any undesirable, negative feelings and provides instant gratification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media divides more than it unites. To what extent is this true</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/social-media/social-media-divides-more-than-it-unites.-to-what-extent-is-this-true/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/social-media/social-media-divides-more-than-it-unites.-to-what-extent-is-this-true/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Social Media divides more than it unites.&amp;rdquo; To what extent is this true? Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/gp-essay-23-social-media-divides-more-than-it-unites-to-what-extent-is-this-true/
It all started with Six Degrees. Launched in 1997, this website enabled users to upload a profile and make friends with other users. It was the predecessor of the many social networking sites to come, and its creation heralded the advent of a new era – an era in which social media would emerge as a new medium of communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stats and Quotes Notes</title>
      <link>/el-notes/stats-and-quotes-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/stats-and-quotes-notes/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents
 Science  Definitions Quotes Examples Stats   Technology  Definitions  Cancel Culture Big Tech AI   Quotes  Cancel Culture Morals and Ethics   Examples  Big Tech Cancel Culture AI  Autonomous Vehicles     Stats  Big Tech and Big Data Morals and Ethics Youth Tech Talent Crunch     Prejudice and Discrimination  Definitions Quotes Examples Stats   Crime and Punishment  Definitions Quotes Examples Stats    Science Definitions Quotes Examples Stats COVID-19 Vaccination   high-income economies with around 16% of the world&amp;rsquo;s population have secured over 70% of 5 major vaccine doses for 2021 Source: Challenges in ensuring global access to COVID-19 vaccines: production, affordability, allocation, and deployment Notes: Research paper on theLancet, found on Fortune.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technology should only be tolerated in so far as it aids the human condition - To what extent do you agree</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/technology-should-only-be-tolerated-in-so-far-as-it-aids-the-human-condition-to-what-extent-do-you-agree/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/technology-should-only-be-tolerated-in-so-far-as-it-aids-the-human-condition-to-what-extent-do-you-agree/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Technology should only be tolerated in so far as it aids the human condition.&amp;rdquo; To what extent do you agree? Question Analysis:
  &amp;ldquo;tolerated&amp;rdquo;:
 If it surpasses the condition: no funding, no research, no technology suckers     &amp;ldquo;human condition&amp;rdquo;:
 Human Needs that can be assisted by Technology?     &amp;ldquo;aids&amp;rdquo;:
 Is technol    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The danger of modern science is that instead of teaching mankind humility, it has made us supremely arrogant</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/science/the-danger-of-modern-science-is-that-instead-of-teaching-mankind-humility-it-has-made-us-supremely-arrogant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/science/the-danger-of-modern-science-is-that-instead-of-teaching-mankind-humility-it-has-made-us-supremely-arrogant/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The danger of modern science is that instead of teaching mankind humility, it has made us supremely arrogant.&amp;rdquo; Comment. In his bestselling book ‘Homo Deus: A Brief History of Tomorrow’, Professor Yuval Noah Harari commented that “during the Agricultural Revolution, humankind silenced animals and plants, and turned the animist grand opera into a dialogue between man and gods. During the Scientific Revolution, humankind silenced the gods too.” In fact, the very premise of Harari’s seemingly outlandish claims is that modern science has made men gods; although the best and the brightest understand that scientific research simply reflects the inadequacy of human knowledge, the accessibility and transformative power of modern science has granted us an immeasurable amount of power which we are wont to abuse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To what extent does social media pose a challenge for the government</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/to-what-extent-does-social-media-pose-a-challenge-for-the-government/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/to-what-extent-does-social-media-pose-a-challenge-for-the-government/</guid>
      <description>To what extent does social media pose a challenge for the government? Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/gp-essay-30-to-what-extent-does-social-media-pose-a-challenge-for-the-government/
The expansion of online social networking has given citizens unprecedented ability to share information, create communities and organize social movements. From a governmental perspective, this could be quite a challenge as social media may be used as a platform to directly challenge the government. It is also a ‘Wild West’ in which misinformation could spread and hatred incited quickly with little means for regulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To what extent has technology had a negative impact on the skill levels of people</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/tech-talent-crunch/to-what-extent-has-technology-had-a-negative-impact-on-the-skill-levels-of-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/tech-talent-crunch/to-what-extent-has-technology-had-a-negative-impact-on-the-skill-levels-of-people/</guid>
      <description>To what extent has technology had a negative impact on the skill levels of people? Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/gp-essay-21-to-what-extent-has-technology-had-a-negative-impact-on-the-skill-levels-of-people/
Mankind has always had a knack for finding the easy way around the most difficult tasks. Once we developed the technology needed to survive the brutal forces of nature in the Stone Age, mankind embarked on a journey of technological advancement in pursuit of a better life. Ironically, in our quest to automate and optimize our processes, we have become heavily reliant on technology, rendering many skills that were once considered fundamental and essential useless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To what extent is artificial intelligence replacing the role of humans</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/ai/to-what-extent-is-artificial-intelligence-replacing-the-role-of-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/ai/to-what-extent-is-artificial-intelligence-replacing-the-role-of-humans/</guid>
      <description>To what extent is artificial intelligence replacing the role of humans? To a limited extent.
Definitions    Word Definition     Role of Humans Tasks that require some form of intelligence and decision making / creative thinking rather than menial labour.    Points  AI today requires human intervention to be maintained  All advanced critical thinking of AI requires collaborating with an AI GitHub Copilot: requires humans to suggest what they wish to code, Copilot is simply a tool (Literally called copilot)   AI requires advanced computations that may not be easily executable in normal settings?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
