<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on Notes</title>
    <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>In an age of rapid technological advancement, is a single career for life realistic</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/in-an-age-of-rapid-technological-advancement-is-a-single-career-for-life-realistic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/in-an-age-of-rapid-technological-advancement-is-a-single-career-for-life-realistic/</guid>
      <description>In an age of rapid technological advancement, is a single career for life realistic? Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/gp-essay-38-in-an-age-of-rapid-technological-advancement-is-a-single-career-for-life-realistic/
A recent LinkedIn survey found that if you are less than 32 years old, you are likely to change jobs at least four times before you reach that age. By 2001, only half of the workforce in the United Kingdom had been in continuous employment for a period longer than four years. Yet another survey by staffing firm Robert Half found that 64% of workers favour what is known as ‘job-hopping’, particularly the younger generation, with 75% of employees under 34 believing in the benefits of job-hopping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technology should only be tolerated in so far as it aids the human condition - To what extent do you agree</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/technology-should-only-be-tolerated-in-so-far-as-it-aids-the-human-condition-to-what-extent-do-you-agree/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/technology-should-only-be-tolerated-in-so-far-as-it-aids-the-human-condition-to-what-extent-do-you-agree/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Technology should only be tolerated in so far as it aids the human condition.&amp;rdquo; To what extent do you agree? Question Analysis:
  &amp;ldquo;tolerated&amp;rdquo;:
 If it surpasses the condition: no funding, no research, no technology suckers     &amp;ldquo;human condition&amp;rdquo;:
 Human Needs that can be assisted by Technology?     &amp;ldquo;aids&amp;rdquo;:
 Is technol    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To what extent does social media pose a challenge for the government</title>
      <link>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/to-what-extent-does-social-media-pose-a-challenge-for-the-government/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/science-and-technology/tech/to-what-extent-does-social-media-pose-a-challenge-for-the-government/</guid>
      <description>To what extent does social media pose a challenge for the government? Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/gp-essay-30-to-what-extent-does-social-media-pose-a-challenge-for-the-government/
The expansion of online social networking has given citizens unprecedented ability to share information, create communities and organize social movements. From a governmental perspective, this could be quite a challenge as social media may be used as a platform to directly challenge the government. It is also a ‘Wild West’ in which misinformation could spread and hatred incited quickly with little means for regulation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
