<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>El-notes on Notes</title>
    <link>/el-notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in El-notes on Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/el-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/el-notes/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/readme/</guid>
      <description>EL Notes If you want, please compile all statistics and data you find in this repository. For EL4131. Additional articles are also appreciated.
Directory Structure ├── Science and Technology │ ├── _index.m │ ├── Tech │ │ ├── Tech Talent Crunch │ │ │ ├── NTU traffic prediction technology bags prizes at Waymo autonomous driving competition - The Straits Times │ │ │ ├── 6,500 new financial sector jobs in 2021 amid shortage of S&#39;poreans to fill rising number of tech roles - TODAY │ │ │ ├── _index.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stats and Quotes Notes</title>
      <link>/el-notes/stats-and-quotes-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/stats-and-quotes-notes/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents
 Science  Definitions Quotes Examples Stats   Technology  Definitions  Cancel Culture Big Tech AI   Quotes  Cancel Culture Morals and Ethics   Examples  Big Tech Cancel Culture AI  Autonomous Vehicles     Stats  Big Tech and Big Data Morals and Ethics Youth Tech Talent Crunch     Prejudice and Discrimination  Definitions Quotes Examples Stats   Crime and Punishment  Definitions Quotes Examples Stats    Science Definitions Quotes Examples Stats COVID-19 Vaccination   high-income economies with around 16% of the world&amp;rsquo;s population have secured over 70% of 5 major vaccine doses for 2021 Source: Challenges in ensuring global access to COVID-19 vaccines: production, affordability, allocation, and deployment Notes: Research paper on theLancet, found on Fortune.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
