<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prejudice and Discrimination on Notes</title>
    <link>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Prejudice and Discrimination on Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/readme/</guid>
      <description>Prejudice and Discrimination According to a 2021 Study by the New York University, the more an academic discipline is perceived to require raw talent or &amp;ldquo;brilliance&amp;rdquo; for success, the more both women and early-career academics feel professionally inadequate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diversity brought about by globalization should be celebrated, not feared. Discuss</title>
      <link>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/diversity-brought-about-by-globalization-should-be-celebrated-not-feared.-discuss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/diversity-brought-about-by-globalization-should-be-celebrated-not-feared.-discuss/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Diversity brought about by globalization should be celebrated, not feared.&amp;rdquo; Discuss. Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/diversity-brought-about-by-globalization-should-be-celebrated-not-feared-discuss-gp-essay-4/
The world today is more diverse than it has ever been. The advent of globalisation, increasing ease of communication and movement has allowed many different cultures, languages, traditions and beliefs to permeate the world, no longer completely separated by geographical boundaries. This increased diversity has led to many positive effects on the world at large such as greater international cooperation, greater economic growth and improvements to the overall standards of healthcare as the exchange of information becomes more fluid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How far is it possible to have a fair and inclusive society in your country</title>
      <link>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/how-far-is-it-possible-to-have-a-fair-and-inclusive-society-in-your-country/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/how-far-is-it-possible-to-have-a-fair-and-inclusive-society-in-your-country/</guid>
      <description>How far is it possible to have a fair and inclusive society in your country? Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/gp-essay-22-how-far-is-it-possible-to-have-a-fair-and-inclusive-society-in-your-country/
In a meritocratic, pluralistic nation such as Singapore, what does it mean for a society to be ‘fair’ and ‘inclusive’? When there is fairness, the treatment of all individuals is not predicated on indicators which are out of his control, such as race or religion. When a society is inclusive, all members benefit from progress and equality of opportunity, diversity is celebrated instead of shunned, and all individuals are allowed to participate in deciding the creation and direction of social institutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How far is the trend towards diversity a positive development</title>
      <link>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/how-far-is-the-trend-towards-diversity-a-positive-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/prejudice-and-discrimination/how-far-is-the-trend-towards-diversity-a-positive-development/</guid>
      <description>How far is the trend towards diversity a positive development? Source: https://www.theknowledgeloft.com/gp-essays/gp-essay-13-how-far-is-the-trend-towards-diversity-a-positive-development/
Many renowned universities such as Harvard are known for admitting students who come from different countries and from different walks of life. The rationale behind this is that their students need to learn how to interact with people with a variety of backgrounds in order to become effective global citizens. Indeed, globalization has made societies today much more diverse since one end of the world is just a plane ride away from the other.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
